dealercarsearch.com 2019-07-19

# Privacy & Cookie Policy - Dealer Car Search

Exit Solutions, Inc. d.b.a. Dealer Car Search ("Dealer Car Search") is committed to protecting the privacy of its customers. This Privacy Policy serves to inform you of the data gathered on dealercarsearch.com (“Website”) and your rights as a user. By use of this Website you agree to the [Terms of Use,] the Cookie Policy, and this Privacy Policy. Definitions in this Privacy Policy have the same definition as they do in the [Terms of Use.]

**_Personal Data_**  
Dealer Car Search must collect certain identifiable personal data in order to offer its business services. This information includes: Customer Name, Physical Address, Phone Number, Email Address, and other information necessary for its services. By providing this information, you consent to Dealer Car Search storing and using the information to provide the services described on this Website. 

Dealer Car Search also collects non identifiable personal data for the purpose of analyzing user interaction with the Website. This information may include information about your device, information about your browser, your IP Address, or other relevant information. Dealer Car Search uses Google Analytics to collect and present data for the purpose of site improvement. To see how Google uses data when you use our Website, please visit www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners

**_Credential Information_**  
User accounts and individual dealer websites are accessible with the username and unique password associated with that username. Do not choose a password associated with any other account and do not disclose your unique password to others. 

**_Information Use And Disclosure_**  
Dealer Car Search uses the information provided to better serve its customers. Dealer Car Search reserves the right to use the information as permissible by law. Dealer Car Search does not sell, license, or otherwise profit off of user information other than described in the Privacy Policy. Some services require providing the information to business partners including third-parties, agents, and other entities. Disclosure to these business partners will only occur if necessary to provide the services offered to the customer. 

Dealer Car Search may sell some or all of its assets in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy or other transaction. In such an event, personal data may be part of that transaction. 

Dealer Car Search will disclose information as required by law in response to a court order or subpoena. 

**_Security_**  
Dealer Car Search implements technical, administrative, and physical security to protect all user information. This Website utilizes secure socket layer (SSL) encryption to protect transmitted data. No method of transmission over the internet or method of electronic storage is perfectly secure and the absolute security of personal information cannot be guaranteed.

**_Cookies_**  
This Website uses Cookies to provide user-friendly features and provide services.

**_Jurisdiction_**  
Dealer Car Search is incorporated in the Commonwealth of Kentucky in the United States of America (USA). The Website and relevant servers which host Dealer Car Search data are in the USA. Regardless of where the end user is physically located, data transferred to Dealer Car Search via the Website will be transferred and stored in the USA and under American law. 

**_Do Not Track_**  
Some browsers advertise “Do Not Track” settings and configurations, however no industry standard for “Do Not Track” behavior has been determined. This Website does not respond to these settings. 

**_Updates To This Policy_**  
Dealer Car Search will update this Privacy Policy at this location. Users are encouraged to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of any changes.

**_Contact_**  
Any questions concerning this Privacy Policy or Dealer Car Search’s use of Personal Data, contact Dealer Car Search at privacy@dealercarsearch.com.

**_Cookie Policy_**  
This website stores small files containing unique information (“Cookies”) on your device. Some of these Cookies are used to store session information so that the website responds predictably to user requests. Our Cookies also may save user preferences in order to present an optimal experience to the user. 

We also use Cookies installed by third-parties in order to provide behavioral targeting of advertisements. The management of these Cookies are outside of our control, however you can learn more about how these third-parties use Cookies and possible ways to opt-out below:

YouTube, LLC You may visit their [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and opt-out instructions [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy#infodelete). 

Google Analytics You may visit their [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en) and opt-out instructions [here](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en). 

In addition to the options above, you may opt-out of most online advertising data collection through the Network Advertising Initiative at [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). 

By using this Website you consent to have these Cookies installed on your device. Cookies may be cleared manually within your browser’s settings. To see your specific browser’s instructions on how to clear Cookies, please follow the appropriate link below: 

Chrome: <https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/9098093>   
Edge: <https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/4027947/windows-delete-cookies>   
Firefox: <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored>   
Opera: <https://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies>   
Safari: <https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/clear-your-browsing-history-sfri47acf5d6/mac>   
If you have questions about this policy please contact us at privacy@dealercarsearch.com
